(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) How do you feel about the award?
I am very happy.
At first, I was not ready for this
happiness.
But when I came to the event for
the first time, I noticed that everyone was
buying.
In that, I wrote a list that I
would definitely buy next time.
We wrote a list today, right?
Something was written in that list.
So, no matter how many obstacles come, he
is my teacher.
When a student hears what the teacher says,
I am happy to say that I have
fulfilled my teacher's wish to improve my life.
Whatever he has taught me, whatever a teacher
teaches me, whatever a student teaches me to
improve my life, through my school, as a
student, I have become a good student who
is proud of him.
I have brought my friend's family here.
Next time, I will try to bring everyone
from their family.
I am very happy.
When you came out of diabetes, how did
you feel at that moment?
At that moment, my friend, my classmate, my
ninth classmate, because of my diabetes, her mother
is a nurse.
Because she is a civilian, she had a
problem.
She was asked to abort her three-month
-old baby.
She had high blood sugar.
She didn't know what to do.
She suffered with me.
She was saddened by my suffering.
Today, she has seen my suffering.
She has brought me here to see the
happiness that has reversed from that.
I am very happy.
Because, after taking insulin, and taking diabetes medicine,
my daughter was born.
I have a daughter.
She has thyroid problem.
I have told this to him.
I have full faith.
I will change my child's life without diabetes.
I have that faith.
When I was diagnosed with diabetes, I had
to take insulin.
I was not even 30 years old.
I was very sad.
I searched in the internet.
I saw his photo.
He said, Do you have diabetes?
I said, yes.
I clicked the app twice.
When I was diagnosed with diabetes, I thought
that I would lose my salary.
I didn't have that faith.
I thought that I would lose my salary.
At that time, I had a one-and
-a-half-month-old baby.
I didn't have any charge.
I didn't leave the three-hour class.
After that, I started to learn about the
research.
I started to learn about the research.
I also began to know about the cells.
I knew that I needed a charger.
I began to renew my body.
I am happy.
My body is happy and my mind is
happy.
The first person who brings joy to everyone
in my circle in my life is Dr.
Farmer.
in my life is Dr. Farmer.
Secondly, Sudhakar sir.
He is the answer to all the questions
in my mind.
Because I always ask each and everyone a
question.
When I was a kid, I used to
get questions like, I am there for you,
I will give you.
I have all the information.
You can take it.
You can move forward in your life.
It is because of his awareness that I
see the HTR and the 1 year course.
So, the only word I speak so far
is health.
If I want to be good, I need
to keep the people around me good.
The word I speak is positive.
When I think positive thoughts, the people around
me are happy.
I see that with my own eyes.
Now, my family couldn't come to buy this.
But my friends have brought their families to
see my suffering.
There may be many in their family.
But for them, I have to become an
angel.
That's what sir said that day.
When I ask each and everyone for an
angel, no one supports me.
But for them, I will become an angel
today.
I will be a reason for them to
move forward in their lives.
That happiness has given me a lot of
happiness in my life.
For that, I would like to thank sir,
his family, all the editors who have been
in support of my school.
I would like to thank everyone.
My coach is Renu Priya when she was
in Therapeutics.
When she was in HTR, Priya, Sailaja ma
'am, and Karthiya ma'am were my full
support in HTR.
I have studied everything in HTR.
Even now, my class is still there.
Even in that, I may not have been
able to write.
But it has been imprinted in my heart.
I will finish writing.
I started writing in 2025.
By 2030, I will finish writing.
I will come to a place where I
can speak like Mr. Mahesh.
I have complete faith in that.
For that, I would like to thank everyone.
If you had not joined Myles School, how
would your life have been?
I would have always been in depression.
That was the first reason.
When I was asked to take medicine, I
would not eat and live my life.
I like to be natural.
I have studied from a farmer's family.
I am a government servant now.
In spite of that, I left my job
and came here.
I left my life in the forest and
came here.
When I thought that diabetes was the reason,
I became anxious.
This has given me a change.
I cannot forget that.
I will continue to support Mr. Mahesh.
I will support him and help him grow.
I have faith in him.
Thank you.